Guide to the Lost Roads Publishers Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- I. January 2007 Acquisition, 20.25; (23 boxes)
  - Audiovisual Material
    - Video Recordings (Box 21)
      - "Lost Roads By Heart #4", 1993 July; YCALMSS726_0006; 1; 00:37:20 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301521)
        David Zimmerman 7/22/93 Jim Whitehead 7/23/93
      - "Lost Roads By Heart #5", 1993 July; YCALMSS726_0007; 1; 00:39:09 (Box 21, Item barcode 39002102301539)
        7/24/93 Deer Arkansas Sesan Burden Shams Kitz Bobby Collins
  - Oversize
    - Book jackets, 8 (Box 22)
  - Restricted Fragile
    Box 23 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Electronic files (Box 23)
      Computer disks are restricted. Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services.
      Available through Access Services:
      2007.ycal.4685.0001: Jacob's Books, Lost Roads
      2007.ycal.4685.0002: Anamorphosis
      2007.ycal.4685.0003: Gill Sans MT Ex
      2007.ycal.4685.0004: Karl Barx
      2007.ycal.4685.0005: Ex voto, The Alembic
      2007.ycal.4685.0006: Ex Voto
      2007.ycal.4685.0007: "Anamorphis Eisenhower"
      2007.ycal.4685.0008: ARK map
      2007.ycal.4685.0009: Dissertation
      2007.ycal.4685.0010: Battlefield
      2007.ycal.4685.0011: LRP
- II. October 2012 Acquisition, circa 1980-2002; 1.83; (2 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Not arranged in any particular order.
  Contains: correspondence, writings, audiovisual, and printed material relating to Lost Roads Publishers.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1286
  Box 25 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Awards (Box 24)
  - Correspondence (Box 24)
  - Events (Box 24)
  - Lost Roads Project, proposal, correspondence and book (Box 24)
  - Lost Roads Publishing Co. documents, Lost Roads catalog 1980, circa 1980 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Lost Roads records (Box 24)
  - News clippings (Box 24)
  - Publications and reviews, 1985-2002 (Box 24)
  - Audiovisual Material (Box 25)
    Box 25 (videocassettes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - The Lost Roads Project, undated; YCALMSS726_0008; 1; 02:04:11 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002102370542)
    - The Lost Roads Project, A Walk-In Book of Arkansas "State of the Word" a documentary videotapes by Forrest Gander, undated; YCALMSS726_0009; 1; 00:48:30 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002102370559)
    - The Lost Roads Project-Sunday Showcase, University of Arkansas, running time 39 minutes, YCALMSS726_0010; 1; 00:39:41 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002102370567)